A Guide to the Virginia Dietetic Association Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1952, TD(8), AD(1) (Box-folder 050:030)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1953, TD(10), pamphlet(3) (Box-folder 050:031)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meetings, 1954, TD(3) (Box-folder 050:032)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1954, TD(10) (Box-folder 050:033)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meeting, 1955, TD(6) (Box-folder 050:034)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meeting, 1958, TD(7), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:035)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1958, TD(1) (Box-folder 050:036)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Health Careers Recruitment Committee Meeting, 1959, TD(2) (Box-folder 050:037)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1959, TD(7) (Box-folder 050:038)
  Letters, Minutes
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Fourth Annual Nutrition Forum, 1960, TD(2) (Box-folder 051:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Fall Meeting, 1960, TD(2) (Box-folder 051:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: White House Golden Anniversary Conference, April 2, 1960, TD(3) (Box-folder 051:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Associations: Executive Committee Meeting, September 24, 1960, TD(1) (Box-folder 051:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Health Cares Committee Meeting, 1961, TD(1) (Box-folder 051:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meeting, 1961, TD(1) (Box-folder 051:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Careers Recruitment Committee Meeting, 1961, TD(2) (Box-folder 051:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1962, TD(3) (Box-folder 051:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Nutrition in Nursing Education Conference, 1962, TD(8) (Box-folder 051:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meeting, 1966, TD(3) (Box-folder 051:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1966, TD(5) (Box-folder 051:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Associations: Annual Fall Meeting, November 10-12, 1966, TD(4) (Box-folder 051:012)
  Meeting Announcement, Meeting Program
- Virginia Dietetic Associations: Spring Meeting, April 19-21, 1967, Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 051:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meetings, 1968, TD(10) (Box-folder 051:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Nutrition Symposium, September 26, 1968, TD(3) (Box-folder 051:015)
  Symposium Invitation List
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meeting, 1969, TD(2) (Box-folder 051:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meetings, 1969, TD(21) (Box-folder 051:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Annual Meeting, 1970, TD(3) (Box-folder 051:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meeting, 1970, TD(3) (Box-folder 051:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1970, TD(14) (Box-folder 051:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meeting, 1971, TD(3) (Box-folder 051:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1971, TD(11) (Box-folder 051:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Fall Meeting, 1971, TD(6) (Box-folder 051:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Annual Fall Meeting, November 7-9, 1973, Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 051:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1979, TD(20) (Box-folder 051:025)
  Minutes, Reports, Award Nomination Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Re-Cap Meeting, 1979, TD(2) (Box-folder 051:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Meetings, 1980, TD(12) (Box-folder 051:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1980, TD(23) (Box-folder 051:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Spring Meeting, 1980, TD(3) (Box-folder 051:029)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1982, TD(5) (Box-folder 051:030)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Meetings, 1983-1984, TD(10) (Box-folder 051:031)
  List of Executive Board Members
- Richmond Dietetic Association: Third Annual Elizabeth Lounds Memorial Lecture, May 23, 1985, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 051:032)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Spring Meeting, 1986, TD(26), AD(2), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 051:033)
  Meeting Reports, Evaluation Forms, Registration Form, Meeting Announcement, Memorandum, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Fall Meeting, 1986, TD(28), Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 051:034)
  Meeting Reports, Copy of Cashier's Check, News Releases, Letters, List of VDA Meeting Guests, Meeting Registration Form, Announcements of Meeting and Lecture, Evaluation Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1987, TD(15), AD(5) (Box-folder 051:035)
  Minutes, Program Schedules, Memoranda, VDA Districts Map, List of Former VDA presidents
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Spring Meeting, 1987, TD(23), Pamphlet(2) (Box-folder 051:036)
  Reports, Survey Forms, Meeting Announcements, Registration Form, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Fall Meeting, 1987, TD(15), Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 051:037)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meetings, 1987, Minute books(3) (Box-folder 051:038)
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1988, TD(18) (Box-folder 052:001)
  Minutes, VDA Executive Board Standing Rules
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1988, TD(15) (Box-folder 052:002)
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1990(January 27), TD(16) (Box-folder 052:003)
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Board Meeting, 1992(August 12), AD(5) (Box-folder 052:004)
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1994(January 8), TD(5) (Box-folder 052:005)
- Virginia Department of Health Professions: Fall Board Meeting, 1998(February 18), TD(116) (Box-folder 052:006)
- Virginia Department of Health Professions: Board Meeting, 1998(June 18), TD(3) (Box-folder 052:007)
  Letter, Notice of Meeting Form
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Regulatory Research Committee Meeting, 1998(November 12), TD(4) (Box-folder 052:008)
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Board of Directors Meeting, 1998(November 13), TD(4) (Box-folder 052:009)
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1999(January 16), TD(3) (Box-folder 052:010)
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Board of Directors Meeting, 1999(March 21), TD(30) (Box-folder 052:011)
  Minutes, Meeting Announcement, Letters, Reports
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Board of Directors Meeting, 1999(March 21), TD(6) (Box-folder 052:012)
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Fall Board Meeting, 1999(April 20), TD(153) (Box-folder 052:013)
  Reports, Letters, Bylaw, Minutes, Memorandum, News Releases
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Board of Directors Meeting, 1999(September 11), TD(46), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 052:014)
  Reports, Minutes,
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Executive Board Meeting, 1999(November 6), TD(30) (Box-folder 052:015)
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Board of Directors Meeting, 2000(January 16), TD(37), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 052:016)
- Virginia Diatetic Association: Board of Directors Meeting, 2000(March 26), TD(31), AD(3) (Box-folder 052:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Educational Exhibits Reports, 1935, AD(3) (Box-folder 053:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disaster Feeding and Civil Defense Planning Reports, 1958-62, TD(19) (Box-folder 053:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Educational Exhibits Reports, 1960, TD(2) (Box-folder 053:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Educational Exhibits Reports, 1961, TD(2) (Box-folder 053:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Educational Exhibits Reports, 1962, TD(7) (Box-folder 053:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Program Chairman's Reports, 1954-58, TD(17) (Box-folder 053:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Treasurer's Reports, 1955-62, TD(49), Payment Slip(1) (Box-folder 053:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Food Administration and Committee Reports, 1956-58, TD(8) (Box-folder 053:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Reports, 1956-62, TD(21) (Box-folder 053:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Nominating Committee Reports, 1956-62, TD(35) (Box-folder 053:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Roanoke Dietetic Association Reports, 1955-1960, TD(15), AD(1) (Box-folder 053:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Tidewater Dietetic Association Reports, 1957-61, TD(7), AD(2) (Box-folder 053:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: List of Virginia Statewide Associations, 1958, TD(6) (Box-folder 053:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Richmond Dietetic Association Reports, 1958-61, TD(16), AD(1) (Box-folder 053:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President-Elect Reports, 1958-62, TD(21) (Box-folder 053:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Press Relation Reports, 1958-62, TD(16), AD(1) (Box-folder 053:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Placement Reports, 1961-62, TD(10) (Box-folder 053:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Education Section Reports, 1959, TD(2) (Box-folder 053:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Education Section Reports 1960, TD(2) (Box-folder 053:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Education Section Reports, 1961, TD(9) (Box-folder 053:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Education Section Reports, 1962, TD(6) (Box-folder 053:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Diet Therapy and Education Section Reports, 1958, TD(13), AD(2) (Box-folder 053:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Diet Therapy and Education Section Reports, 1959, TD(5) (Box-folder 053:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Diet Therapy Section Reports, 1961, TD(5) (Box-folder 053:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Food Administration Committee Reports, 1959, TD(4) (Box-folder 053:025)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Committee on History Reports, 1960s, TD(51) (Box-folder 053:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Food Administration Committee Reports, 1962, TD(2) (Box-folder 053:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Career Guidance-Public Relations Reports, 1959, TD(6) (Box-folder 053:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Career Guidance-Public Relations Reports, 1960, TD(3) (Box-folder 053:029)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Public Guidance-Public Relations Reports, 1961, TD(7) (Box-folder 053:030)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Public Guidance-Public Relations Reports, 1962, TD(5), AD(2) (Box-folder 053:031)
- Blue Ridge Dietetic Association: President's Reports, 1958, TD(6), AD(1) (Box-folder 053:032)
- Blue Ridge Dietetic Association: President's Reports, 1959, TD(4) (Box-folder 053:033)
- Blue Ridge Dietetic Association: President's Reprots, 1961, TD(5) (Box-folder 053:034)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Membership Reports, 1958-62, TD(81) (Box-folder 053:035)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Annual Report, 1970-71, TD(1) (Box-folder 053:036)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Lists, 1952-98, TD(89), AD(2) (Box-folder 053:037)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Report on Installation of Officers, 1970-1971, 1970, TD(4) (Box-folder 053:038)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Strategic Plan Reports, 1997-2003, TD(25) (Box-folder 053:039)
- Reports on Child Daycare, 1988-1989, TD(49) (Box-folder 053:040)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Lobbyist Selection Committee Report, 1993 (March 31), TD(20) (Box-folder 053:041)
- Virginia General Assembly Interim Report, 1998, Book(1) (Box-folder 053:042)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1966, TD(8) (Box-folder 054:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1969, TD(17) (Box-folder 054:002)
  Guidelines, Pre-Registration Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1979, TD(22), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 054:003)
  Bylaws, Letters, VaDA Lines
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1980, TD(6) (Box-folder 054:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1981, TD(7) (Box-folder 054:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1982, TD(31) (Box-folder 054:006)
  Bylaws, Reports, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1983, TD(54), AD(3) (Box-folder 054:007)
  Letters, Meeting Time Schedule, Scholarship Application Form, Bylaws, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1984, TD(76), AD(15) (Box-folder 054:008)
  Bylaws, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1985, TD(9) (Box-folder 054:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1986, TD(32), AD(6) (Box-folder 054:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1987, AD(2) (Box-folder 054:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1988, TD(84), AD(2) (Box-folder 054:012)
  Bylaws
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1989, TD(9), AD(1) (Box-folder 054:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1995, TD(3) (Box-folder 054:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1996, TD(6) (Box-folder 054:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1998, TD(4) (Box-folder 054:016)
  Memorandum, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Standing Rules of the Board of Directors, 1999, TD(23) (Box-folder 054:017)
- Tidewater Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1978, TD(27) (Box-folder 054:018)
- Blue Ridge Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1979, TD(10) (Box-folder 054:019)
- Northern Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1980, TD(24), AD(2) (Box-folder 054:020)
  Bylaws, Letters, Reports
- Richmond Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1983, TD(34), AD(1) (Box-folder 054:021)
- Southwest Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1986, TD(5) (Box-folder 054:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Media Representatives Activity Reports, 1993-94, TD(121), Newspaper Articles, Flyers(4), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 055:001)
  Reports, Letters, Memorandum,
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Media Representatives Activity Reports, 1995, TD(120), Newspaper Articles, Newsletter(2), Flyer(1) (Box-folder 055:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Media Representatives Activity Reports, 1996, TD(52), Newspaper Articles(12) (Box-folder 055:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Media Representatives Activity Reports, 1997, TD(15), Newspaper Article(3) (Box-folder 055:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Public Relations Reports, 1994-98, TD(34), AD(2), Newspaper Articles(2), Envelope(3), Notecard(1) (Box-folder 055:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report: A Critical Look At the Question of Licensure, 1983, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 056:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report:, 1986, TD(19), AD(15) (Box-folder 056:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report: Submission at Public Hearing of Health Regulatory Board on Need for Regulating Dietitians, 1986(June 12), Report(1) (Box-folder 056:003)
- American Dietetic Association Report: Licensure Information Packet, 1986-88, Packet(1) (Box-folder 056:004)
- American Dietetic Association Newsletter: Nutritionist Licensing, 1988, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 056:005)
- Virginia Council on Health Regulatory Board Reports; The Need for the Regulation of Dietitians and Nutritionists, 1987, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 056:006)
- Dietetic Currents, Volume 14 (Number 5), 1987, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 056:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Licensure Report, 1988(November 8), TD(4) (Box-folder 056:008)
- Virginia Board of Health Professions: Report on the Need to Regulate Dietitians and Nutritionists in Virginia, 1994, TDoc (21) (Box-folder 056:009)
- Comments on the Regulation of Dietitians and Nutritionists, 1994-1999, Report(1) (Box-folder 056:010)
- Comments on the Regulation of Dietitians and Nutritionists, 1994-99, TD(291) (Box-folder 057:001)
- Final Study Report: Study of the Appropriate Criteria to be Applied in Determining the Need for the Regulation of Any Health Care Occupation or Profession, 1997(July 1), Report(1) (Box-folder 057:002)
- Virginia Board of Health Professions: Report on the Policies and Procedures for the Evaluation of the Need to Regulate Health Occupations and Professions, 1998, Report(1) (Box-folder 057:003)
- Virginia Board of Health Professions: Report on the Study of the Need to Regulate Athletic Trainers Pursuant to Senate Joint Resolution 122, 1998, Report(1) (Box-folder 057:004)
- Virginia Board of Health Professions: Resolution Request Form, 1999, TD(2) (Box-folder 057:005)
- CCN(Certified Clinical Nutritionist) Examination Packet, 1994-99, TD(120) (Box-folder 057:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Licensure Survey, 2003(March), TD(42), Transparencies(9) (Box-folder 057:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Licensure of Dietitians Background Paper, 2003(August), TD(14) (Box-folder 057:008)
- West Virginia Board of Licensed Dietitians Newsletter, 2003(September), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 057:009)
- State Professional Regulation Update Report, 2003(October), TD(1) (Box-folder 057:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Pamphlet: "The Registered Dietitian in Virginia", N.D., Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 057:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Guidelines for Contacting Legislators, N.D., TD(23) (Box-folder 057:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Photos, 1950s, Photos(18) (Box-folder 058:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Photos, 1960s, Photos(4) (Box-folder 058:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Photos, 1970s, Photos(33), Negatives(14) (Box-folder 058:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Photos, 1980s, TD(1), Photos(60), Negatives(37), Newspaper Clipping(1) (Box-folder 058:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Photos and Newspaper Clippings, 1990s-2003, Newspaper Clippings(31), Photo(1) (Box-folder 058:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Photos of VDA People, N.D., Photos(12), Newspaper Clipping(1) (Box-folder 058:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association National Nutrition Week Certificate of Recognition, 1977(March 6-12) (Box-folder 059:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association National Nutrition Month Certificate of Recognition, 1982(February-March), Certificate of Recognition(1), TD(4) (Box-folder 059:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Cook Book Project, 1999, TD(122) (Box-folder 059:003)
  Report, Letter, Minutes, Recipe Form, Evaluation Form, Guidelines
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Certificate of Award Samples, N.D., Certificate of Award Samples(4) (Box-folder 059:004)
- Carolinas-Virginias Hospital Conference Pamphlet, 1952(April 24-25), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 060:001)
- Indiana Dietetic Association: History of the Indiana Dietetic Association, 1964, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 060:002)
- Puerto Rico Dietetic Association Newsletter, 1971(April-June), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 060:003)
- District of Columbia Dietetic Association Newsletter, 1971(winter), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 060:004)
- State of Hawaii: Proclamation of Nutrition Awareness Week, 1971(September 19-25), TD(1) (Box-folder 060:005)
- Ohio Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1983, TD(7) (Box-folder 060:006)
- Virginia Health Council: Health Careers Reference Manual, 1989-90, Book(1), Pamphlet(1), TD(5) (Box-folder 060:007)
  Letter, Contract Form
- Virginia Council on Coordinating Prevention Report, 1990-92, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 060:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association:, 1919- 1949, TDoc (28) (Box-folder 060:008)
- American European Dietetic Association Pamphlets, 1990(September), Pampnlets(2) (Box-folder 060:009)
- National Dairy Board and Other Associations Leaflets, 1990-92, Leaflets(9) (Box-folder 060:010)
- Colorado Dietetic Association: Board of Directors List and Statues, 1991-94, TD(3) (Box-folder 060:011)
  Memorandum
- Massachusetts Dietetic Association: Report on Nutrition Services Improve Health and Save Money, 1919 - 1993, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 060:012)
- Virginia Public Health Association: Procedures Manual, 1996-97, TD(26) (Box-folder 060:013)
- Kansas Dietetic Association: Bylaws, N.D., Booklet(1) (Box-folder 060:014)
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1948-51, TD(10), Postcards(4), Envelope(1) (Box-folder 061:001)
  Letters, Receipt, Memorandum, Application Form
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1952, TD(5), Envelope(1), Pamphlet(1), Newsletter(1), Photocopies of Newspaper Clippings(11) (Box-folder 061:002)
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1953, TD(11), AD(1), Envelope(1), Booklet(1), Pamphlet(1), Photocopies of Newspaper Clippings(21) (Box-folder 061:003)
  Letters, Reports, Constitution and Bylaws, Convention Program, Asheville Invitation Letters
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1954, TD(16), Envelopes(2), Pamphlet(1), Photocopies of Newspaper Clippings(16) (Box-folder 061:004)
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1955, TD(23), Envelope(4), Photocopies of Newspaper Clippings(16), Convention Program Pamphlet(1), Certificate Care(1) (Box-folder 061:005)
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1956, TD(20), Photocopies of Newspaper Clippings(4), Convention Program Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 061:006)
  Letters, Reports, Ballot Form
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1957, Photocopy of Newspaper Clipping(91) (Box-folder 061:007)
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1958, TD(4), Envelopes(2), Newsletter(2), Photocopy of Newspaper Clipping(1) (Box-folder 061:008)
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1959, TD(5), Envelopes(3) (Box-folder 061:009)
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1961, Photocopies of Newspaper Clippings(2), Program Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 061:010)
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1962, Photocopy of Newspaper Clipping(1) (Box-folder 061:011)
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, 1966, TD(1), Photocopies of Newspaper Clippings(2), Newsletters(2), Program Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 061:012)
- North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurses Association: Materials from the Scrapbook, N.D., TD(3), AD(1), Photocopies of Newspaper Clippings(9), Postcards(3) (Box-folder 061:013)
  Letter, Reports
- American Dietetic Association: Historical Documents, 1934-44, TD(40), Newsletters(4), Program Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 062:001)
- American Dietetic Association: Programs and Manuals, 1937-50, Pamphlets(3) (Box-folder 062:002)
- American Dietetic Association: Manual for Executive Boards of State Dietetic Associations, 1971, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 062:003)
- American Dietetic Association: Bylaws, 1978-83, TD(174), Pamphlets(3), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 062:004)
- American Dietetic Association: State Associations Manual, 1983, Manual Book(1) (Box-folder 062:005)
- American Dietetic Association: Newsletter, 1984(May), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 062:006)
- American Dietetic Association: Membership Census Report, 1986, TD(41) (Box-folder 062:007)
- American Dietetic Association: Leaflets, 1986-90, Leaflets(12) (Box-folder 062:008)
- American Dietetic Association: Report on the Reimbursement and Insurance Coverage for Nutrition Service, 1991, Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 062:009)
- American Dietetic Association Report:"Position of the American Dietetic Association For Replacements", 1991, TD(4) (Box-folder 062:010)
- American Dietetic Association: Outstanding Dietetics Student Awards, 1994, TD(13) (Box-folder 062:011)
  Letters, Reports, Award Selection Forms
- American Dietetic Association Report: "Implementation Guidelines For Creating the Future ADA's 1996-1999 Strategic Framework", 1996, TD(13) (Box-folder 063:001)
- American Dietetic Association: Board Certified Specialists, 1996-1997, TD(31) (Box-folder 063:002)
  Letters, Reports, Recommendation Forms
- American Dietetic Association: Annual Fund Campaign, 1996-1997, TD(9) (Box-folder 063:003)
- American Dietetic Association Report: "ADA Positions Supporting the ADA Strategic Framework, 1996-1999", - 1949, TD(7) (Box-folder 063:004)